Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Director's Files of the Mount Wilson Observatory, 1900–1926; 10; 11 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_02, Carton 2, Reel 81–100, Carton 4)
  - Paul Stroobant, 1905–1922; HaleGE_10_00_169_06; 32 pages (Box 169, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 742 to 775.
  - S: Miscellaneous, 1904–1920; HaleGE_10_00_169_07; 157 pages (Box 169, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 776 to 933.
  - Toshio Takamine, 1921; HaleGE_10_00_169_08; 4 pages (Box 169, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 934 to 938.
  - Taylor-Hobson Company, 1909–1913; HaleGE_10_00_169_09; 36 pages (Box 169, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 939 to 975.
  - Taxes, 1905–1907; HaleGE_10_00_169_10; 7 pages (Box 169, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 976 to 983.
  - J. Miery Teran, 1907–1908; HaleGE_10_00_169_11; 8 pages (Box 169, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 984 to 992.
  - Thompson-Starrett Company, 1909; HaleGE_10_00_169_12; 11 pages (Box 169, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 993 to 1004.
  - Elihu Thomson, 1907–1923; HaleGE_10_00_169_13; 28 pages (Box 169, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 98, frames 1005 to 1033.
  - Tiffany and Company, 1913–1923; HaleGE_10_00_170_01; 36 pages (Box 170, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 20 to 56.
  - Otto Toepfer und Sohn, 1905–1922; HaleGE_10_00_170_02; 87 pages (Box 170, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 57 to 143.
  - O. H. Truman, 1915–1919; HaleGE_10_00_170_03; 25 pages (Box 170, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 144 to 169.
  - H. H. Turner, 1913–1921; HaleGE_10_00_170_04; 45 pages (Box 170, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 170 to 215.
  - T: Miscellaneous, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_170_05; 115 pages (Box 170, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 216 to 331.
  - U. S. Coast and Geodetic Survey, 1904–1919; HaleGE_10_00_170_06; 83 pages (Box 170, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 332 to 415.
  - U. S. Geological Survey, 1919–1920; HaleGE_10_00_170_07; 14 pages (Box 170, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 416 to 430.
  - U. S. Naval Observatory, 1912–1913; HaleGE_10_00_170_08; 6 pages (Box 170, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 431 to 437.
  - U. S. Weather Bureau, 1905–1916; HaleGE_10_00_170_09; 36 pages (Box 170, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 438 to 474.
  - Union Iron Works Company, 1905–1916; HaleGE_10_00_170_10; 234 pages (Box 170, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 475 to 709.
  - Union Tool Company, 1914–1916; HaleGE_10_00_170_11; 64 pages (Box 170, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 710 to 774.
  - University of Chicago Press, 1905–1915; HaleGE_10_00_170_12; 153 pages (Box 170, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 775 to 930.
  - U: Miscellaneous, 1905–1921; HaleGE_10_00_170_13; 33 pages (Box 170, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 931 to 964.
  - E. A. Varela, 1911–1914; HaleGE_10_00_170_14; 9 pages (Box 170, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 965 to 975.
  - A. Van Maanen, 1911–1921; HaleGE_10_00_171_01; 117 pages (Box 171, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 99, frames 976 to 1094.
  - P. J. Van Rhijn, 1913–1922; HaleGE_10_00_171_02; 16 pages (Box 171, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 20 to 36.
  - V: Miscellaneous, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_171_03; 40 pages (Box 171, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 37 to 77.
  - Charles D. Walcott, 1905–1913; HaleGE_10_00_171_04; 39 pages (Box 171, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 78 to 117.
  - O. R. Walkley, 1916–1917; HaleGE_10_00_171_05; 23 pages (Box 171, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 118 to 141.
  - R. James Wallace, 1905–1910; HaleGE_10_00_171_06; 64 pages (Box 171, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 142 to 206.
  - Warner and Swasey, 1904–1920; HaleGE_10_00_171_07; 33 pages (Box 171, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 207 to 240.
  - H. P. Warren, 1922; HaleGE_10_00_171_08; 5 pages (Box 171, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 241 to 246.
  - William C. Weber, 1921–1922; HaleGE_10_00_171_09; 26 pages (Box 171, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 247 to 273.
  - William Wesley and Son, 1904–1910; HaleGE_10_00_171_10; 89 pages (Box 171, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 274 to 363.
  - Westinghouse Manufacturing and Electric Company, 1915–1919; HaleGE_10_00_171_11; 30 pages (Box 171, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 364 to 394.
  - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1919–1920; HaleGE_10_00_171_12; 6 pages (Box 171, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 395 to 401.
  - Walter T. Whitney, 1912–1916; HaleGE_10_00_171_13; 38 pages (Box 171, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 402 to 440.
  - C. J. Willett, 1913–1914; HaleGE_10_00_171_14; 4 pages (Box 171, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 441 to 445.
  - E. B. Wilson, 1914–1919; HaleGE_10_00_171_15; 30 pages (Box 171, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 446 to 476.
  - H. C. Wilson, 1909–1921; HaleGE_10_00_171_16; 27 pages (Box 171, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 477 to 504.
  - Ralph E. Wilson, 1918; HaleGE_10_00_171_17; 25 pages (Box 171, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 505 to 531.
  - W. H. Wright, 1916–1920; HaleGE_10_00_172_01; 59 pages (Box 172, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 532 to 592.
  - Max Wolf, 1908; HaleGE_10_00_172_02; 11 pages (Box 172, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 593 to 604.
  - Frank S. Wood, 1917–1918; HaleGE_10_00_172_03; 4 pages (Box 172, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 605 to 609.
  - R. W. Wood, 1908–1915; HaleGE_10_00_172_04; 66 pages (Box 172, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 610 to 677.
  - W: Miscellaneous, 1904–1923; HaleGE_10_00_172_05; 126 pages (Box 172, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 678 to 804.
  - Anne S. Young, 1917–1920; HaleGE_10_00_172_06; 5 pages (Box 172, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 805 to 810.
  - P. Zeeman, 1908–1921; HaleGE_10_00_172_07; 109 pages (Box 172, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 811 to 920.
  - Carl Zeiss, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_172_08; 26 pages (Box 172, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 921 to 947.
  - F. R. Ziel, 1910; HaleGE_10_00_172_09; 3 pages (Box 172, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 948 to 953.
  - XYZ: Miscellaneous, 1904–1914; HaleGE_10_00_172_10; 127 pages (Box 172, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 100, frames 954 to 1083.
  - John L. Wirt, 1905–1920; HaleGE_10_00_173_01 (Box 173, Folder 1)